Memorization Bread for the Exams!
Brought to you by: Ko-Fi.me/OrangeFlash
There's a problem!
I'm in trouble now!
Oh no!
Doraemon, I hate you!
I have a problem and yet you ignore me!
What's your problem?
Good question!
In fact, there are Japanese and maths exams tomorrow.
So that's why you are carrying your pillow and water kettle.
Although It has nothing to do with the exams..
Long story short, I'm in a big trouble now!
What?
Help me out!
Don't tell me that you are going to just sit there and do nothing, do you, Doraemon?
Please help me...
I'm probably going to get 0-marks...
Please
Just use this fan!
Doraemon is the best.
Tell me about it!
Use that fan to blow off the school.
Thanks, but wait, what's blowing off school about?
What kind of joke is that?
I can't blow off my school, gimme something else.
Then how about using the animal light to turn your teacher into a gorilla?
Thanks!
Stop fooling around and be serious!
What are you saying?
You are the one who don't study hard it's your own fault!
I will study hard, so please rescue me this time.
Please do something!
If I get 0 in my exams, I will run away from house.
You're so hopeless, let me use the Memorisation Bread.
Memorisation Bread?
Press the bread on to the book and the content will get memorised by the bread.
Then swallow it up!
Then you'll be able to remember everything that's written on a page.
Do you wanna try?
_ x2=6?
Bingo!
_x5=10?
Absolutely correct!
Just memorize all the exercises from textbook.
You should be able to write exams easily.
Gimme more!
I can get 100 marks on the exams now.
Ah, I tore a very important page!
I tore it to use as tissue paper to sneeze on!
You're so unbelievable!
Whose bag is that?
I have to memorize my friend's notebook.
Can you please get me more Memorisation Bread? I'm gonna visit my friend.
I see.
Sure.
Glad I can help you.
Why, thank you.
Please take a look!
How dirty!
I study hard!
Huh? You don't want my notebook?
it's really hard to eat this kind of Memorisation Bread.
Shizuka-chan's notebook is always this clean, I am going to memorise it
It won't be that hard if everything is this easy.
I am quite good at memorizing things.
But you are the most forgetful person in class. You don't say....
OK, let me show you.
I'll eat up this telephone book.
I can memorize all on the first page.
Test me!
Please start!
Name it!
No. of Ai?
1234567
Indeed! You are right!
No. of Ms. Fukiku Keiko?
9999876
You are right, amazing!
No big deal.
it's hard not to get 100.
I envy you!
Yes, as long as I have this bread, that is.
Nobita-kun, feel free to have some snacks.
I have brought lots of Mochi, so help yourself.
Mochi is very tasty!
I can eat a lot.
You're just eating and reading Manga, when are you gonna study?
Now it's time to eat more Memorisation Bread!
What's wrong?
I have to let the food in my stomach get digested.
You have eaten too much.
Sorry, can I borrow your notebook?
I'm home!
Welcome home!
It's dinner time, come on!
I don't wanna eat!
Aren't you hungry, Nobita?
You are the one who wanted to eat cheeseburger.
But....
You must eat!
I made a special big one for you, so dig in.
Special big one?
I'm full!
Nobita, have you memorized everything?
Not at all!
I gave you tons of Memorisation Bread, but you...
You forced me to do things I don't wanna do?
Ok, but please don't get angry.
I have borrowed the notebook back, I will eat now!
I really can't take it anymore.
Have some water and swallow it.
I can't!
I really can't do this anymore.
is it OK to have 0 on your exams?
Don't wanna!
I know. I will let you eat all of them by any means.
Are you done yet?
Nope!
Not yet!
Are you done yet?
No!
What's wrong, dad?
Nobita has been in the bathroom from an hour!
He ate too much and is having stomach ache now.
But that's bad!
You pooped all the pages you ate...
So you have to re-eat from page 1 now!